visit-montenegro.com 2016-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Visit Montenegro - Breathtaking Beauty

#### VISIT-MONTENEGRO.com

#### CUSTOMER AND VISITOR PRIVACY POLICY

Visit-Montenegro’s.com privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by Visit-Montenegro.com anytime you interact with Visit-Montenegro.com, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase our products and services, or when you call our support associates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at Visit-Montenegro.com, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

**Why we collect personal information**  
Why do we collect your personal information? Because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest news, information, special offers, services, and events that you might like to hear about.

**What information we collect**  
There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service. For example, if you subscribe to our newsletter, participating in our actions and contests, or purchasing a product. At such times, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; and information relating to a support or service issue. We collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and where you use your computer — to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. We also collect information regarding customer activities on our website www.visit-montenegro.com, and on related websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them.

**When we disclose your information**  
Visit-Montenegro.com takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that Visit-Montenegro.com does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with legal entities within the Visit-Montenegro.com group globally who will safeguard it in accordance with Visit-Montenegro.com privacy policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for Visit-Montenegro.com to make certain personal information about you available to companies that Visit-Montenegro.com has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Visit-Montenegro.com to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with Visit-Montenegro.com policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the Visit-Montenegro.com website.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

**How we protect your personal information**  
Visit-Montenegro.com takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

**Integrity of your personal information**  
Visit-Montenegro.com has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided.

**Cookies and other technologies**  
As is standard practice on many corporate websites, Visit-Montenegro.com website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We also use cookies and other technologies to make sure that our online advertising is bringing customers to our products and services. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. And we use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us.

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Visit-Montenegro.com will not use the information collected to market directly to that person.

**Our companywide commitment to your privacy**  
As we said, Visit-Montenegro.com takes protecting your privacy very seriously. To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate these guidelines to Visit-Montenegro.com employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

Visit-Montenegro.com website has links to the sites of other companies. Visit-Montenegro.com is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

**Privacy questions**  
If you have questions or concerns about Visit-Montenegro.com Customer Privacy Policy or data processing, please [contact us](http://www.visit-montenegro.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").
